She came in extolling, talking loud
Hold the side count, hold the drop
Lizard wreckage, call your man
This wholeness, the knife, the dirty
Be the same
Step two, poison me
Step three, say I'm just worried
While you mob in prayer
Step four, my persecution
When somebody checks your guess
Off your hatred as
Plug in my camera
Hold on a second
hold on hi guys hold on i'll fix it sorry oh my god i look like kramer
i'm sorry hi thanks for being here um where's hopefully jamie comes so um you know i feel
terrible because you know maybe it's like my stuff but you know people are you know jamie's like
such as she's like the nicest person like anybody that knows jamie like she's like the
She's been with the show since the beginning. She's like, you know, top mod even though she doesn't really keep people out
You know, I don't she doesn't really need to she's like and she likes everybody or she's almost people
but
maybe it's just because of me or something but
People are being like so mean to her and she doesn't deserve it and
You have a problem with me. Just take it out on me. Don't leave Jamie alone. I don't understand what the
dealio is with that like um
She's being called a cunt. She's being called. I mean, it's like another, you know, it's like
You know, she's being called a cunt by a cunt. I mean
We all know Christine is one but not Jamie's not
Christine some old bitch
Me know bitch, right?
Jamie's sweet and Jamie
Jamie also has like, you know, she was in a terrible accident and she has as a trauma and
memory problems and it's like it's really out of line go after her but you
know even me saying this is like people are probably gonna go oh yeah so I mean
it's hard it's hard you know but yeah I think Nancy had a good point she's like
people need to learn empathy you know how is that you know I don't know the
golden rule right it's like not too difficult treat people like you'd like
to be treated so yeah for example like
when I go say hi in money for 20s chat who I like you know I'm happy to promote and
and all this and I'm like the only person that's not a mod there and then
bronze bronze bitch decides to time me out for 24 hours because of some
being his own feefies about things his own personal issue oh okay so I guess everyone left okay so
and uh and who else and Christine I mean there's bullies and that's just the beginning I mean
it's like there's a lot I mean it's like I'm pretty sickened by hi Jamie I was just
you know letting people know it's like you know I don't understand why so what happened they
were who was it calling you a cunt like and for what reason like I mean it's like there's no reason
to it's just ridiculous hold on I'm still small hold on
I guess they didn't want to.
Sig was here.
I've never seen, I haven't seen Sig in a while.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, this is my cat that hates me
and my cats are attacking me.
I don't know if he's like, you know,
this woman I like to call Big Back Kate.
I don't know.
She had a post called, or it was just like me.
I don't know why they have to like, you know,
she always is like, you know, they're criticizing me
making use of AI for like, you know, creative endeavors,
but they have no problem using it to like,
themselves to like you know take a picture and make me look like Cyrax or
you know or make my house dirty and all this kind of crap right and but they
yeah they have to they had a picture of a oh there's the North and this is the
cat that hates this one of the cats that hates me right yeah but they have a
picture of like my you know my cat biting me my cat on my arm and me like
What my other cat his name is Tux and he's been kind of he's almost take a half barrel cat
No, it's like if he just got back here and I gave him catnip and sometimes when cats get on catnip
They get a little bit aggro right Lenore knows because Lenore's a little catnip fiend
right
You like catnip. Yeah, she's a little catnipping, but Lenore doesn't bite Lenore, you know, she would never bite
Yeah, I'm tired of it too, and I'm gonna probably do something about it. But yeah, so Lenore
Hi, Lenore. Oh
Oh, so this is one of the cats that hates me, right?
And they're like and then it's like they have these people and calm empty on the post
Oh, well, of course, it's biting him because, you know, they're starving.
That's all they have to eat is him.
And then, oh, well, why do that?
Because, you know, they can just get another rat outside, you know, very occasionally.
Occasionally, they'll catch one.
And they love cats.
I mean, it's like, you know, cats are like little hunters.
And it's like they have this instinct that wants to, like, that's why people
have like little mouse toys and stuff like that.
I know it's like I'd rather have a mouse toy.
I don't want a little mouse in my house.
There's not rats.
It's like, you know, they're little mice, little field mice.
and then they like to come and they play with um they think it's a toy you know they because
but they have plenty of toys but they like the like the kind of live one that makes squeaky noises
and then they kill it and they're like oh what happened they don't really understand even they
don't like they don't like to eat them usually i try to grab it as soon as they can they usually
get tired of it and then i'll just like you know pick it up and throw it in the trash and stuff
or if it's still alive they'll try to you know rescue occasionally right but um
But yeah, so anyway on on catnip cats can get a little bit
Aggressive and so when I pulled the cat in a bag away. Hey, he swatted, but you know what last and he and he wasn't
Very touchy when he first came in. You know what now he is now. He likes to be pet
This is not Lenore. This is this is tux. I'm talking about and he likes to be pet and stuff and now and he's
Very sweet and I he was born under my TV set
I mean, it's like it'd be like saying. Oh, you know, it's like, you know, okay yells at you
It's like oh does your kid hate you? No, it's like, you know, sometimes they you know
People have like a little emotions and stuff. It's because I show so much of myself that you happen to see my cats
You know swat at my hand
Sounded like I was like, you know, you know injured or anything or you know, it's like I can I know how to handle cats
You know, I woke up with a horrible, you know, a succubus
Burned, you know three lines into my arm that I still the scar from that. I was fine with right so anyway
I think I still have that scar you can see it
People are and if people are still like, oh, he did that to himself. I don't know if you can see it
There it is right there see this three lines
Yeah, so that's miss panther. Oh, yeah
Are you pretty are you beautiful? You're beautiful, huh? Oh, you like when you I mean these are the cats that hate me, right?
but uh
Yeah, and then these are going my cats love me. That's not how I talk. That's how you know you talk
You know you hail Billy whatever bitch. I mean, it's like geez my cats do love me, right?
Anyone knows me they know my cats love me, right? Okay. She's welcome
Yeah, I need to I need to you know I said I would post something for I'm sorry. I haven't done it yet, but here's the
There's a link
Anyway, all right, baby
But you know my cats are very gentle. Yeah, she was she's just to climb the curtains
She likes to all my cats like to cuddle with me under the blanket, right? Oh
I don't think the best cats and it's just
If you know if you I don't know it's like it's so it's like they're either just flat out lying. They're using stupid
You know image
They don't just you don't just show me as me. It was like I mean I show myself
I mean it's like we've seen pictures of you of them, right?
Kate, you know, you see what she looks like
Jamie Nick. Oh, yeah, hold on. What does that mean?
Cuz Mammy I weren't you're one of the people that I just I had banned and I unbanned you but is everybody saying neck
What does that mean? Just let me know so I can know whether
There's a penny wise in your photo. Oh my god. It's like penny wise in hell or something
Jamie neck. What does that mean? You want a neck with her? I think it's James. Well, Jamie's Jamie's not interested. Okay, maybe
Okay, oh so anyway
This is how my cats are and I'm not like I'm not like forcing her my lap. I took her off my lap
She would jump right back in it. Wouldn't you would you?
Yes, you would
This cat is a kisser. Do you remember how to kiss her? So it's a kisser. Okay. Here's um, here's the INX. Let's welcome INX
Hey there. I hope Brandon joins. I know he's on. Yeah, that bitch is crazy. Crystal. And
you can share the video that he just posted. I'm able to post again on Sunday. I got a
copyright for some song I added to my shorts a week ago. So I can't post till then. But I've
been recording Crystal because I'm tired of this bullshit. Again, we got to record her.
Um, Batboy Breeze, who she puts down, say, oh, he's gay, he's gay, all this shit, he's cool.
She had us fight for a long time and he's a witness to all her weird shenanigans
Also, you might want to use my videos to show who the real crystal is
She she made a fake case against another guy
She tried to force to stay with her because she wants a baby so bad also on one of the recording
She's told me that she made a new guy on Facebook. She's just wanting to have a baby. That's all
It didn't work out with the other guy either because they all turn on her because she's crazy and she's a cop caller
Why doesn't she go to Toys R Us and get a new baby?
know right what happened to those plastic dolls though because I mean she's
insane and then I heard that she's all on Kate's live all night see she doesn't
have a life and they're saying send the links to her brother James I have
communication with him now they don't want her in their lives at all they've
been done with her since the pandemic they say that she has mental issues and
she does this
And to her family and uh, and uh, you can share all the videos on see I'm gonna private everything
I can't unprivate it until Monday. I mean inx I was listening to like, uh, you know
You appear on her show and she actually said something like she wants to get I think she said she wants to get
Q a tombstone of with an angel with backs maxi padwings
She's crazy. We did not talk about q. She's a liar
See we talked about other people. She's you know, she's a liar
It wasn't about Q at all and and and that recording he just posted on his while you can share it
Okay, um, and I'll I'll I'm private the other videos too. You might everybody needs to see the truth
She hasn't changed one bit
There's still a lot of videos of all these victims of her that she met on on facebook
And she'd be in discord and she'd be blasting them on calling the police on them. There's a lot of videos
And there's a channel with your channel is what it's so it's a great full
2026 grateful gr at e f u l
2026 if you're saying there's a video there that I should play right now
Yeah, but see I private everything for her because she said she we weren't going to mention each other and there
She's mentioning me everywhere and everybody's clipping everything and they're going to her family her her brother James
I just spoke with him
Well here, okay, so Brandon has the video I guess I can play brandon and yes you can play he just put it there
Yes, play that
And that's a recording our last recording. That was just a few days ago
And then I blocked her and I messaged her that I don't want any part of her bullshit and leave my name Nancy and
Jamie all these people's names out of her mouth
We just want to clarify. They're different Nancy's and Jamie's there's not not reality Nancy. No, not her
It's it's Nancy being Nancy who's never a part of any of this stuff
She she does real life all the time with her husband and her son who just graduated
Uh, you know, it just, um, this one, yes, that's the one and that's, and that's what
she, yeah.
I should play some of this?
Yeah, go ahead and play it play.
That's a call.
That's the last call with her if you want to bashing Astro mom and Ella and listened
to her.
There was no talk about Brandon, let me know if you want me to, you want me to pause it
or anything.
No, go ahead and just go ahead and play it all Astro always talk shit about all of us
But Ella is a very shady though Crystal because remember she she because I even asked her
She hates Astral so why is she talking to her?
See how shady she is. She's one of us that heard to me about what she did and how she you know
She knew about the microwaves
See she's agreeing with me. Where's she talking about Brandon? Nothing, but she talks about everybody
See I told you she's talking shit about Ella that she's repeating everything. She says to Astro
She's crazy. She always plays victim. It's Ella doing it and why is she in contact with her? She's still in contact with her
See that's how messy they are. They're probably talking about bride
Yes, he talked shit about
I think I was trying to talk shit about bride and I was wondering yeah
Well, why was she crazy bride cuz he didn't even know much about bride before yeah
Hold on here. We go
You know what yeah crystal be careful because remember I'm telling her be careful because she plays victim
Don't and like and you're the one that busted her when she messaged you with that account
Admit it. Yeah, she makes with the Gwen name and the last
No, I'm not and I am I'm so in it
Background on like because I don't think everyone's familiar with who Ella is
Well, we don't need to go into who that is right now
Bitches are crazy. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I mean, I know she's crazy. Yeah
But where are we talking about Brandon? See she's in communication with these people is the issue trying to start a war with everybody
Here she's agreeing and saying how bad she is
And still in communication with her. That's how bad and nasty. Yeah, she has no wife. She lives her drama. She doesn't have a real life. She doesn't meet real people.
She's fighting again with that guy on Facebook and I'll show you that video. She sent it to me by text where she's calling the police on him.
Yeah, and there you'll see a lot of videos and that they got it from discord and people shared it.
that she does is to all these guys that she hooks up with on Facebook.
She's desperate to have a baby, right?
And she was kicked out of the military.
And on Renee on top, who now goes by on Tropolis,
she's the one that busted her out for the lies against Beanna.
Bad Boy Breeze came out and told the truth.
He's right now sharing a video and tagged me to it
because she was on live with lying clumsy.
Line about it that oh, yeah, well, I did call her baby was that to warn her about
Brandon would know she we're talking shit about Ella
You know beta all of these people she wants them gone cuz she and believe she's clean of YouTube
She has no life outside of the internet. Yeah
Not even the prom prom queen of youtube. I mean she's not she's like she's yeah
And see i've got proof worse her proof of me calling her about brandon
I'm proving it and that's why I ran her off two years ago
How dare her try to get in contact with me again because she was turning on my friend nancy
And victoria honey cut
They were done with her everybody. She's saying she's oh, yeah, I did call her but she's only called her to show her the receipts on brandon
There was no receipts. This is a call. This is our last call. There's more I'll go ahead and post everything on Monday
And I'm gonna private everything that she begged me to private
She's insane her own sister Jennifer who I talked to said that she's always been way off since she was a kid they never got along with her she has serious mental issues Brandon was telling the truth and maybe I should play that recording where her father says that you know that she goes nuts on him.
And she'll show up at their house banging on their door.
He'll open the door and she'll start yelling at him.
And when he gets upset with her, because she goes crazy
and threatens to call the police,
you'll get on the police, get on the phone with the police,
and then she'll be hitting herself in the face.
He's hitting me, you know, for the police to hear
so that they believe that he's, the dad's hitting her.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, well, you know, just everything I've seen of her,
Yeah, she's pretty crazy and
She talks about it. She needs to be in a mental hospital. That's where she needs to be
She was before because even that guy rick
They did a whole live and they contacted the police and they were all in a group call and the police told us all that
They already do a check on her every month because her parents, you know always calling her she has issues
her neighbors complain about her her cat the other cat died because she didn't want to get it help
she was busy on live and the cat was suffering in her closet in the dark and she wouldn't take
him to the vet and then she sent her dad to put him to sleep because she couldn't handle it there
she her dad shot the cat huh no no they he took him the pet him put down because he was getting
sick and she wasn't doing anything for him and
And I remember we were posting about that. Yeah, um, she, you know, she declawed her cat, which is like, yeah
She declawed the new cat. She doesn't know how to take care of animals
Recently she did that and then it was in her new cat. Oh my god
Yeah, and she knows it's wrong all because of her furniture
She calls me an animal abuser and she actually declawed her cat. I mean that is yeah
She declaws her cat and she let Milo die because she was on live and people were yelling at her
It's I go take care of your cat. Oh no, he's fine. He's just old
And then then then later her dad's taking him to the vet and she didn't want to be involved with any of that and they had to put the
Mallow down she was taking him to the vet
He was suffering there at the end and she just let him be in his closet and he was
Yeah, it's just sad. I mean, I saw a video Alexander played where it's like, oh, oh, you know
She's in this in this house and there's oh, there's the cleaning lady
Like this lady on the on our hands and knees on the floor like scrubbing that's her mom
That's how she treats him and the dad that's what her brother told me that her parents are like scared of her
Yeah
And then she cleans her house and her dad
Is kind of like scared of her that's what james said and jennifer i talked to her to.
I mean they've been done with her and then she's the one that sent me a dm between her and her and that was her dad's brother.
I know that her dad sister.
Trying to shit on her dad saying what a bad person he is and this is us talking about him because he's a piece of shit
Or that's what she was telling me on the phone and when she sent it to me
It was her DMing the aunt about the dad
He's this and that or whatever and the ants only response was
crystal your
Family says that we're not allowed to say your name in their home. That's that was her only response in that weird
So why are you showing me your ants response?
And now the aunt passed away. She didn't even bother to go to her funeral. She was dancing in her car going out to eat
Yeah, oh my god
yesterday, I played you know a video of it was gamble
Talking to Aaron Carter, and I've never seen that video, but it's like and then he's he's referenced Crystal
So they're they mean that so they were so they're in this group and this group is like, you know
They target people it looks like from it's pretty obvious in the video that they target people
to like basically to to ruin the reputations or to i don't know if there's like blackmail or
extortion involved or something but like they were you know he's he i guess he posed as like a
person on instagram asking for like a nude photo and then of course then it's like then he says oh
well i'm a 15 year old girl or something you know it's like not even there's not even a real person
involved it's just him saying it and then he then he can call people a pdf right i mean it's like
What is their game? I mean, it's like, it seems like they have some kind of weird thing
they're doing. Like, you know, it's like suicide or something. What do you think is the, it
looks like a pattern.
I don't know. It's just, she's sick and like-
For trying to get views, you wanted views because he has no content. He's a fucking nobody.
They got rejected by Ice Poseidon.
So they're so desperate
Yeah, she tried to do a live a few years ago at a at a bar or pool hall and she seemed so awkward and uncomfortable there
And all she cared was about the live. She's afraid to see her neighbors
One time there was a dog out and we were talking and she said all the dog
I don't know who he belongs to I feel bad for him and I said well
Maybe he belongs to your neighbor and she said I don't know I hadn't seen him before and I said well, can you go check?
And she said, Oh, I don't know them. It's like she's been living there for a while and she doesn't know them
Right. I mean, I think she's definitely socially like awkward and awkward. Yeah crazy and they do welfare check on her monthly
That's what they told us all
Yeah, because they were trying to and then Wilbur he's good. She's accusing him of stuff. I'm cool with him
And so he just added me on IG, but Bad Boy Breeze13, you can tag him, he's a nice guy.
I've heard of him, I've definitely been in my chat, I know for sure I don't know.
Oh he has, he's a good guy and that's another one that she fucks with.
You know, all of a sudden she hates him because he won't have shit to do with her in the whole year.
So he's a bad person because he's been done with her.
Yeah, yeah, the shit she put him through and look at what she did with Wilbur and King
Had them fight and call the police on each other and and it's all her and this is all she lives for she has no real life
You know, she doesn't know how to have a normal conversation with people
It's always something about somebody this that or and she thinks she's famous
Because that video that I'll show you from Chelsea
In the video she says I didn't know who this person was accusing my boyfriend of you know
Doing something to her and I've never met her and when I did talk to her she was telling she this is what she said
She said the crystal was telling her that she's gonna be famous because she thinks she's gonna be a Britney Spears
That's why huh obsessed with Britney Spears
Yeah, I mean she really believes that and she keeps saying famous in her mind. She thinks she's gonna be a famous celebrity
She's crazy. I didn't realize she was that sick until I talk to her brother James
Absolutely delusional
Yeah, just very delusional and they say that, they admit that she is and they're just upset
that the dad lets her treat him the way that she does, yelling at him, calling the police
and hitting herself in the face when he tries to call the police on her to make it look
like he's hurting her.
She's insane.
Yeah, didn't she like, you know, wasn't there something about she poured like some like a root beer or something in the toilet and said something?
No, it was pea soup. It was pea soup green. I mean, it was obvious
It was me and somebody else and she wanted us to go to
Discord to defend her because they were calling her out because remember Gamble said she lied
About being pregnant and and the images she showed they did the google google image of it and it belonged to somebody else from
And there she kisses his ass, it was him and Shane Coyle that called her out and she'd cry and you know and she's just very obsessed with Gamble.
She really thinks that he's in love with her and she said that he was gone because she was gone. That's how crazy she is, she's really delusional.
Well, yeah, now she's going for like, you know, I think well now she's going for Hugh who's you know younger than yeah
And now she's posting pictures of AI pictures of them together when he can't stand her, you know
He's a watch he's gonna turn on her. He'll open his eyes
I guess what like I seen her on some show I see I keep seeing her on clumsy's and then I see her on
Yeah, and clumsy is shady as fuck. I didn't realize that he lied about beta beta
I saw that communication that he finally said he was posting with this broken phone
Yeah, nowhere in there was there any mention of what he's about any miscarriage or is why he lied he lies about everything
That was nothing there was nothing because I was a child. Yeah
prove
And he's a liar psyche he lied yesterday because I've never had a conversation with him
All we did was talk shit about beta, you know
That was it, but he had the nerve to tell Sam and salmon came on
And now that he's exposed for actually being gay and lying about it because he even admitted it to site
What's it?
Good times and other people so that's out. Yeah, he's been telling people that so now
They called him out for it and Tommy James to Tommy James called him out on his live yesterday. He is gay
Yeah, I didn't know that I don't know much about him, but he's shady as fuck because he's got a criminal
Record everything but what I didn't like was salmon came on his
Was trying to get on his panel and that asshole lied to him saying that I talked to him about his mom
I don't know anything about salmon's mom. I was mad that he was using an old old fat pick of me
And I use the picture that I found the cue would use and it happened to be his mom
You know of course, I'm gonna fight back, but I don't know anything, but I've never had a discussion about the mom
I don't know her and he had the nerve to say yeah
She said this about your mom or whatever. It's like I didn't even know his mom and I've never had a talk with him
He's I can show all our DMs because the only thing we did was DM only
Yeah, and he's a piece of shit
But when I he never showed proof of of beta and I'm not trying to defend beta because she's a bitch though
You know and she's done a lot of shady shit, too
And but she nowhere in those DMS was there any mention about his wife
Or any miscarriage or anything he lied about that so he's a liar
He lies. He's a punk. He was blazing.
Chris K was blazing.
Oh, Chris K was blazing him last night.
Yeah, Chris K. Chris K is bisexual.
I mean, yeah, but he was glazing.
He was glazing clumsy last night.
Say, no, I fucked that, dude.
I told him I'm not gay.
Um
He was on stream all all this morning until
Crystal was on to and then for her he privates her to live so she's crazy. I'm gonna put everything out on her
She's a fucking crazy bitch. Her family is watching everything
I'm gonna start targeting him because he was glazing gambles all gambles cool. He's all oh gambles smart
Well, at least five lives out of Chris K saying he wants to come to my house and do chatter bait with me
So yeah, I mean, it's like what what is he talking? Oh, there's oh, we have a great
You know what? I even have an old
I have an old DM from him from her from four years ago
That somebody sent me and they wanted me to send it to Gamble and in there. She's
Lying and saying that Gamble is trying to kill her
I'll even show that she lies about everything
I'd be she's a psychopath. Well, is this Brandon Q. Is that Brandon Q right here next to me? Yeah. Yeah
Okay, the pimp daddy brand-in-cube the the pimp daddy who you the pimp daddy Mac, right? Yeah, what's up, bro?
Yeah, yeah, Karen. Yeah, she's full of shit man, and I don't like her
What's the name Chris K was glazing clumsy dude all night dude?
He was laughing at a video that
Steven that's his name the RG guy was posting about him dancing and calling him gay
I mean that was on his live two months ago. What video?
Um, it was about Jay dog was in and they said oh, he's in a gay club dancing
People were asking me in the chat room they were saying hey, um, we bet you don't have balls to go in that gay bar
Actually, oh, I bet you I will I don't care. I'm not you know, I'm not
I'm comfortable with my sexuality as far as like exactly.
And then gay people don't bother me.
I don't have no issue with gay people.
Yeah.
And there he is.
He's the one that is and he's over there calling other people out
for that same they are when he is right.
You know and he's just a piece of shit. I didn't realize I thought he was cool, you know
Do you want to go to it you would you would you take me to the gay bar out there?
Well, yeah, but there's like one in like the three-city area. There's it's like, you know, they're maybe long beach
It's like there's not even one in the area. I've never been to one in this area
So I would okay. Well, you know all the spots to take could go to so you would have to show me around
So I'm thinking this weekend psyche. What do you think?
That'd be cool. J-Doc can dance though.
Yeah, I can. He looks like we had a good time.
Yeah, because I was drunk. That's what life's to learn.
So we could have fun. You know, it's all laughs and fun. It's not no...
Exactly. You know, but it's not...
Yeah, exactly.
It's not no dangerous stuff. It's not nothing bad. It's all fun and games.
Like, I mean, Psyche, we're going to have fun. I'm going to dance with Psyche. Psyche, you want to dance?
Okay, I'll dance with you.
Oh yeah, we're going to dance. We're going to do something.
Yeah, I got for sure. You know what? Yeah, psyche, we're doing this. We're doing this for sure this weekend. Guarantee. We're gonna do this. I promise.
This is a promise. This is a promise. I'm not leaving you hanging, psyche. This is a promise. This weekend...
So I saw you in Kate's chat last night, you know,
Yeah, and then Kate, you know, believe in her bullshit.
Come on, Kate, open your eyes.
You'll open your eyes soon because I felt for that too.
For the past year, you know, thinking maybe she changed
because she's always all for me.
But look at the truth.
I wasn't Kate's chat last night because there was a rumor
going around that I had said about Kate getting.
Hey posted that of me last last night, you know, oh shit. I didn't see that
Yeah, she says that I use AI
But he's delusional
She's delusional
Bullshit
My cats love me psych psyche racks
says they are
carrying into him
Um, a daily, maybe something they wouldn't, and then they wouldn't, you know, attempt to kill you.
I don't know.
So, I'll take that down.
So, yeah.
Thank you.
So, you're down for Friday night?
You're down?
Are you down?
Yeah, for sure.
Thank you.
I can't hear you, psyche.
Your mic was a little...
Yeah, for sure.
I'll be there.
For sure.
Okay, um, so I come to your I come your house, okay?
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna put my email address in the back and you can email me your
Your your info like your address your phone number that I'm gonna text you
It's gonna come from a different area code number. I'm gonna text me. I'll be like, hey, this is J dog
And then you can send me the details, like your address, phone numbers, stuff.
And you know, that's when we were, you know,
we were on a hunt for a cat to hate me.
And it's like, one cat scratched me with the keys
and he was taken out for like a year and a half
and he's a little bit wild.
And then he, he was high on catnip
and I reached over, took the cat in the bag
and he kind of swatted me a little bit.
But that, I guess, equates to my cat's starving to death
and hating me.
Okay, I put it in the backpack.
That's my email psyche right there.
Go ahead and email me.
Yeah, just add me to your Heggers book and then,
Email me and I'm going to be my number and I'll go ahead and um, just don't give my number out to nobody like
Yeah, and then um, yeah, you can just email me all the stuff or text me or call me or however
No problem. All right, thank you. I'll see you later, man. It's a loose everybody
I mean it's like I'm having so much you know these people I mean it's like and they're so there's such followers and
They just believe whatever they're totally so many of these people. I mean, I see very few people
you know having
and so
They don't even pay attention to like the truth and it's like I know you both are exposing a lot of truth
and
Yeah, and she's bringing Nancy's name up again
Nancy has a real life with her husband because when we talk, she's actually so busy with her family. Her son just graduated with top honors.
You know, he's really, really smart. And yeah, he's got the thing he graduated so early and they were out riding e-bikes and she was showing me the battery that it takes a long time to charge. And here, Crystal would be calling me about bullshit
bashing everybody. It's like she bashes everybody behind everybody's backs and I don't know just sick.
I'm just happy, like I'm happy I'm banned from her show, I'm happy I'm banned from
Bita's because it's like I don't really want to have contact or did we discuss, I mean
it's like these people have put me through, through pretty much hell and you know, I'm
you know
Yeah.
They'd like to talk about me, but I'm not allowed to defend myself and and then it's pure lies
And so I know that they lie. I mean, yeah, Kate is so I found out all her info bro everything dude where she works
Courts and stuff. Yeah, they have it out
They just mean because I like Kate's and I just can't believe
Head of the the campaign the boycott or whatever gets my show
and is talking about you know constantly trying to report my channel and get my channel make you homeless get your evicted
Yeah, I mean, it's like and then she were you know, Tony works for her. I mean, or sorry, Benjamin, you know, whatever is the Benjamin
Yeah, it's like he works for her
Um as one of her goons she calls it and it's like and then it's like, you know, she doesn't want to
Have all this stuff coming out about her the why is she
I mean, she looked at me for an hour just talking about me and everyone's saying oh my god
Oh and saying my city and and getting like really really personal talking about my family
And then saying, you know, oh, you know
I mean, it's just like it's a tack attack attack and I was kind to her
Like that's the thing is like I would have her on my show the only as soon as you know
We had it some kind of disagreement and she has to go up about this up predator protect
Yeah, fine, and then she figures out works and then she gets I mean when you say something like that
What wait does anybody like a pro predator like no, but it's like it's not like they don't know the story
And that's like what's frustrating because I will stand up for the truth. I just want the truth out
I just want there what really happened
And uh, and it's like and I can see very clearly what these people are doing. She is a predator. She is a predator
She has stalking charges harassment charges
Manufacturing drugs fucking all kinds of shit
How that military thing to show that how you left the discharge or whatever it says on there
Yeah, and and somebody even her ex friend even has a copy of it. It's honorable
It shows on there dishonorable because, you know, that she was left because she was accusing
a sergeant from the boot camp of trying to sexually assault her.
And then she and then they were looking into that and then they put her in the office
She never made it to Iraq and it shows that on her DD 14 or whatever that she sent Renee busted her
It's all out there and she told me I can use the videos and I will I just want that bitch to leave my name out of her mouth
Stop lying. Yes. I've recorded you on that text now number
You shouldn't have called that number
So, I actually knew that, but yeah, not on my real number, you know, like Alex has my
real number, Brandon does, you know, and a couple other people that never shared it,
and family and friends, there's no recording on there, but on the text now, and yeah, it
just, you can, it's just an app that just goes along with the text now.
because they're deciding to go so hard against me and with all this stuff and you know,
I mean, you know, basically, you know, I'm put up against a wall where it's like, you know, trying to take
To give me perma ban for like a botting or, you know, whatever and
Which is I say I have nothing to do with at all and I can have no control over what happened like that
Right, nobody's botting you who's bought if you had bought bro. If you had bots, it would be hundreds dude
There's no fucking bots. You can't even I mean, she's already she said well here
that she said that she um you know like last week she was like oh well we should like start
botting psyche's chat and so with anything people than he does and then um and then she went um I
got last night she was saying oh well Brandon leaked a receipt that um he's botting psyche's chat
and I'm trying to warn psyche you know but I know she's not so it's like I think that it's all
No, she's full of shit. You can't get bots. You can't just say oh you can't even say 200 bots, bro
It has to be like 500 a thousand, bro
Yeah, you can that you can do that they do bots to do what traffic bots and they do
Just to have you so it says that you have like 500 but when when you do that it's gonna say like 500 a thousand three thousand
A dollar or something like that try to bought me and then try to report it and say look
He's body and then try to blame it on you till we all turn against it. I mean, it's like very obvious like what they're doing
I'm gonna learn that the body now. They didn't know about
comment bots and stuff like that and then she's like, well, you just put you just put your chat on um subscriber only and then they
Can't bother. Yeah, that doesn't help for the traffic bots
It only helps for the the comment bots and there's I don't have any comment bots
You don't have any bots. You don't have any bots you would it wouldn't say 40 or 50
For sure or Tony or something like that, I mean and or and then I saw Brandon like there's somebody with your exact like profile
Picture and it's like your same account and stuff like that imitating. Yeah, she would she put it on her status
That's crystal, and that's supposed to be gamble doing it. Yeah. Yeah, that's gamble. Yeah, yeah
And that's like that's like that's not allowed to like, you know be imitating somebody is like
your exact profile to it.
Gamble's obsessed, bro.
He's obsessed, dude,
because I showed how fucking ugly he is, dude.
That dude is.
Yeah, he's got a lot of weight.
I just saw that picture.
It's like, damn.
He's skinned.
What is wrong with his skin?
I even asked the AI what's wrong.
I said, what's wrong with this person's skin and face?
And it's like, well, it's kind of blurry, but it looks like they have a lot of hard lines around their eyes and all of this and that and
covered in blemishes
I mean these people have all just like came at me. I don't I didn't know them before anything
Well, I am way better looking than him dude. He looks like shit compared to me. Yeah, I mean, it's like
Ridiculous, I mean, it's like even looks better mirror gambles face. Who looks better?
Very puffy. He looks very puffy and like very puffy. But his eyes. Do you see how his eyes are like sagging the skin like around his eyes is like black and like
Drooping bro. I've never seen that dude. Never seen that dude on somebody that's 32 years old, bro
And he's involved with his dad. It's what I
It's like all his skin is just like like gravity is pulling like it's just like
It's fucking crazy dude. That's drugs. He's a drug. Yeah crack rock. Chris told me all the drugs. He does he does mess
He does everything bro. Yeah heroin fentanyl Zanny's
I mean you can tell he's like part of some like, you know extortion or ring or something like that or any was they target celebrities
They target people that they think have any popularity and they try to get cloud off of just basically destroying people's lives
And it's like yeah expose that part of it because you can really see it in the Aaron Carter
Video and celebrating death too, and I don't know why they don't like me. They're like whole gamble went after him
He went after everybody they praise all these other people who are actually bad Attila
All these people he did the same thing. Oh, you would do live streams Attila's a pedo
They glaze him. Oh, it's ill but no, but it till is bad. He's been drunk
I know it's like, you know, but that's where they want to silence people is because that they have even
They have much worse things like they're hiding and they don't want it
They don't want people talking about them because and so they'll still they'll say oh well
They're a predator, you know, and they'll try to
Manufacture evidence that to make it look like that desperately and then the sad thing is this like such a thing that most people are
Believe it or be afraid to go against anybody that says, you know, because it's like, you know, it's one of those virtue signaling
Things that people do right. It's like, oh, you know, because they're like who's really pro nobody's pro PDF, right?
It's like so it's like always gonna be an easy win
But now it's like people are catching on to the game
And uh, it's like it's like really taking attention away from actual real victims and things like that. Yeah, why doesn't he go after real pdm?
So why doesn't he go after his mom? His mom got arrested
For drinking with little boys
Her students. Why doesn't he go after his own mom?
Yeah, well, you know, it's like
I mean they have these people I do have something to actually hide and it's like, you know
Everything's been said about us, but it's like and then it's like but then they go after us to yeah
Prevent us from speaking about what's happening. What's really happening and going on crack rock Chris was telling him
He's all why are you messing with Brandon? He's all you want to catch a predator. He's all go in the next room next to you
There's a predator right there. Go. Why don't you go catch your dad?
Well, yeah
God is that yeah, we'll catch your dad in the next room
Well, yeah, it's like crazy like I see
Yeah, and you know more about these people. I mean, I don't I don't know these people
What is Jamie's cowboy saying they want their names left out? Who's bringing up your name? Nobody's bringing
Nobody's bringing you up Jamie's cowboys
Again, I'll say they're different Jamie and Nancy and so it's like but people get
That's right. I want to clear that up for someone because they were saying why why is Jamie in there with the Cowboys name?
Talking about being this ex-friend
Jamie said that's not her. That's somebody else. Why are you sending me screenshots? That's somebody else?
No, that's it and then reality Nancy's is definitely a reality Nancy's a catfish
Yeah, that's what they said. I've talked to her before. She seemed cool. I have her number. We used to talk
I like that Nancy to talk to a few times. So, you know, she acts cool. Yes, you like cool, but she'll be talking shit
She's talking shit right now. She'll talk shit about everybody when she was called out for being a catfish on gandals and something about
Her son or daughter. I don't even remember. Well, I'm saying these two can never leave drama alone. No, they can't leave us alone
You know, they stalk us or banned by Alex this year. You're very two-faced Nancy
Oh, you want me? I'll give you her number a band. Yeah, you want it? I love all her communication
Very two-faced and she's all in chats 24 seven with drama and
Always Nancy you're a nobody reality Nancy catfish
You know and then the other Nancy it was well known. She's you know, all the people alone if they leave me alone
it's like when we get back into a corner and
slandered and
Attack constantly
Unprovoked
Eventually bite back, you know
And so I tell them to leave me alone and I'll stop talking about them stop going in chats
Yeah, she needs to chill Nancy's not about you we're talking about another Nancy that everybody knows of
Yeah
We can make a distinction so we'll call Nancy reality Nancy will call
Nobody's who's threatening a dog somebody's threatening a dog
Let's be quiet Nancy trying to start trouble again like you do in every chat and then get banned and then you wonder why are you?
Why are they lying though, bro? Why are they lying saying that we're trying to leak shit?
Nobody's leaking anything
That we're trying to dox people who no
It's pretty cool. That's a different person. I don't know why people are saying cuz yeah, yeah
Back crystal brought Jamie back to mod for her and then she turned on her
She used her against Vita because Vita and that Jamie were close friends at one time
Look reality Nancy. We're not talking about you. We're talking about another Nancy and that's Karen's friend
We're not gonna she's not talking about leaking Nancy's number
She's talking about showing the calls and the videos not linking Nancy's number Nancy is her friend
He's like a daughter to me. She's not involved in any of this
She's a good person and she does real life and she has an amazing husband
I mean they go eat like riding the Starbucks with their son, you know, and they just do real life
She's hardly on at all
She did go into Alex's the other day because Alex put a nice video on me. That was really sweet and she
Yeah, who are we talking about doxing? Who are we talking about doxing Bay? Who who?
Who who's Bay?
Some weird guy that has a big beard and he wears mustache and catfishes dudes on YouTube
That fish is
Is that true? Oh my gosh. No, this is about reality Nancy
I wish she'd be quiet because I hear that she you know what people show me or her chats or whatever
So, I don't know. No, there's a good Nancy there Nancy be Nancy and check out her channel. She's very beautiful
the gars
used to be close friends with Vita a long time ago and
He lost all of them
Yeah, nobody's not seeing anybody nobody's threatening nobody. They're just lying bro
That's what people do in chat say say shit
So then they think that other people will read that and believe it in the meantime there's reality Nancy trying to touch
No, I mean maybe you stop reality Nancy calm down
I'm not talking about her and we're not your friend. The Nancy we're talking about is your friend. We're not threatening her. Yeah, it's a it's a it's a good Nancy.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't I don't I think we're talking about because there's another Jamie to and then we're trying to say is the Jamie that crystal was using as a mod.
And then when Crystal says her name, she just says their names Nancy and Jamie and and I see a lot of confusion there, too
It's like what a giant reality Nancy did this when she's bitching about particularly comment on it
but all I'm saying is that
That people should just leave each other alone. Yeah, they need to leave me alone
I mean, you know, because at first I didn't know him and Brandon, he's actually a good guy and he is a very intelligent like we all talk about the space stuff that's going on.
And he's in Albuquerque where I went to high school that was there for two years.
And yeah, it's interesting.
So he talks about real stuff, you know?
He's not, nothing weird, no weird combos about kids
or anything, nothing.
We talk about real stuff and with garlic sometimes.
And that's why-
Some people will see we're reacting sometimes
to what's being said, but also it's like, you know,
and we've all been slander so much that it's like,
we've got a few people that know about us,
but it's like they have these huge groups of trolls
going after like us everywhere like as like you know like all kinds of shit so it's uh
it's uh it's definitely they think that they have some kind of well even that on a crystal show
they're like well let's let's do this let's like accuse everybody of uh you know of this and then
All the people that are against that will come to our group and then the other group will look stupid
And so it's like this whole like a little strategy they have
And then she wants to talk and can you remove this? Can you at least private it? Why I'm showing the truth on you
Look at that. Those are
It's because yeah, she wants you to hide the truth and hope you delete it
And then then you'll be like, yeah, it never happened and never happened
And I private them and I can't turn private it until monday until that
uh that's it's supposed to be over with by monday the music uh copyright or whatever
on my shorts so yeah that's true that she's fine stuff on her and then there she is yapping
her mouth because she can't help it she's crazy yeah she's delusional she and she needs to keep my
name out of her mouth dude she needs to keep my name out of her mouth
And she does that for her sister Jennifer said that she can't that she caused problems with her marriage kids and she said he was a disaster that she was horrible with them because they're they're close the brother and sister they won't have shit to do with
And they won't speak to her and I didn't have her saying so in text
Yeah, by the way, this is the place that everyone's saying I stole from and so why am I still going in there and they're so friendly to me
I stole I mean I did not feel from the store on my stream because they
Like my car didn't go through and then the new cashier like said it went through and stuff
And and they're trying to say I'm some kind of feet. I still coffee now. I still coffee and a cigar
That lady was kind of rude. You could have gotten her in trouble by talking to your supervisor because you you wouldn't
Yeah, it's like you know it's a little corner store, but but yes you've reacted
She's like she's like oh you're stealing and then the girls like no, he wasn't he wasn't like
Um, so, I mean, but there's still, I mean, everyone else there is nice to me, but yeah, why would I be going in there if I actually still, why would I try to like burn myself out of a corner store for a dollar to guard this?
You were in a rush though, too. It was just, yeah, you were like surprised like when she said that you did something or whatever she was thinking about. But yeah, she was kind of wrong.
Just how they present things and everyone believes this shit. They believe the AI photos about me.
I mean, they're so crazy.
I mean, they're on there.
I'm like, are these people crazy?
Yeah, I beat up, you know, my care.
I was really high.
This was in 2021.
I was doing a lot of drugs though.
I mean, I was, you know, really bad, but.
And I was high as fuck and you could tell and she's now look at her at least I don't have skin tags or a crater face
That was fucked up out of my mind. Yeah
You know way better than her. She was like
Not at all then but she you know they still show an old picture of 2016 when I got really fat
It was after my mom died. It was just hard, you know, and I know was getting diabetes
I was getting high blood pressure
all that's been gone since 2018 and now I'm kind of underweight and I mean why do you think I got
sick last year it was just really bad and you know and now I have to drink more water though but
I got sick I wasn't eating and I got sepsis
And the medicine the doctor are not even on camera and their pictures are fake. I mean we use our real pictures
That's my recent picture I FaceTime even with the tiller I FaceTimed with him on IG
on it. Um, yeah, I'm private it because why did, uh, um, um,
beta and, uh, Sam and ignore my request to come up with me.
I'll do it with you guys do it. Let's come up. I said,
I have shitty makeup on on that picture. Yeah, that, you know,
because I don't like to come up without makeup shit.
Because, uh, we saw what they looked like. We might think
differently about
you know people might think oh because he has a nice picture where he's like in a studio with
yeah i look great man but yeah you know and i just got to see him as his whole body fits in his
his whole body fits in his in his uh profile picture is i mean so he adores i'm not even sure
but i don't know if you guys know joe shippley like joe shippley's a really nice guy
I don't know if it's because he was supportive of me, but they're saying, oh well, you know, 20 years ago
When the Blair witch project came out he was he was you know, he had he had like a
Like a black kid in his lap like it was some kind of like like dirty thing
I mean, it's like I mean these people of their minds are so disgusting and
I know right. It's just
man
And it's so sick that they want to slander even him and he's been like so cool with everybody
I mean, I'm really sick of it. I'm really sick of it. Like, um, and you know, that's why I
am happy to expose what's really going on because
It's not what people think. I mean people are just such followers about it
It's like that that word seems to like just hypnotize some people into thinking all these things that they have these
conspiracies where the whole world is
Is doing and all the celebrities are eating
Babies and and you know all this kind of stuff and it's like pretty ridiculous
It's like I mean it's like I think celebrities were probably laughing at the dumb American public
You just believe everything in a national inquire or or whatever show they're watching. Oh, they do do that shit
They do do that shit that already got exposed bro. They said fucking
Epstein and shit bro was eating fucking like
80 pounds of fucking human meat, bro fucking beat, bro. I mean that's a lot of
Beef jerky so these like oh, and then it'd be like we need more beef jerky, and then they're talking about oh
Public venues and that's huge larger scale. They say it is they maybe are you know in some laboratories
I don't even believe in there's fucking cannibals, bro. They're cannibals, bro. It's already been proven, bro
It's black and white, you know where you're welcome. Oh, yeah, even Vladimir Putin even Vladimir Putin says that he's all
Yeah, all these fucking cannibals. He's all they're done. He's all they've been feasting on the he's all he's all the leaders of the west
He's all the leaders of the west. He's all the leaders of the west
They consume human flesh and then stuff their pockets
Well, the money ever heard of if you ever we have a behavior of Baba Yaga
She's like, you know, she's in russian and she craves russian blood, you know, where's the russian blood and so
There's camels, bro. Yeah, they but that should already got exposed, bro
Trump uh or ebstein it was so much on how he was gonna acquire that me and he's like, oh
Are you gonna walk this one over the border?
I mean, that's very...
It's all real, dude. It's real, bro.
No, and then that thing is all real. Let's put it that way.
No, it's...
It's real. It's something they didn't want to come out and it came out.
I know about the adrenochrome, and that's like, you know, from a...
Adrenochrome? No, that's fucking fake. That's fake, bro.
Okay, that's fake, but...
That's fake, bro.
Yeah, okay
Not everything real everything that's in the Epstein files is real everything that's in the Epstein files is real
That's what I'm saying. Okay. Okay
We're entitled to agree to disagree, you know, it's like I have I think that a lot of stuff is
manufactured for social engineering and for also just to like, you know, like I don't know like
There's certain things, but I know I can't really talk about some of the stuff because
it is like you know stuff that people go missing now you gotta be careful speaking about that stuff
look at those scientists that are going missing but it's like yeah do i believe in school shootings
no i think that most of the stuff is psyops and this is not a popular opinion that's a thing oh
look guys look at my window here's the window today yeah but the abscene file that's not a
That's okay. Well, you're you know, you but you know, I
You can be sure opinions
I personally think that if there's hundreds of 14 year old girls being flown into an island to give massages to billionaires
And their parents don't know about it for months and months and months and actually this woman
Jill is saying went to which is up with to junior high schools to recruit them
I think that's a little bit far-fetched, but you know, you're free to believe what you want to I'm not gonna
How is that far-fetched, bro?
because parents don't know their daughters are getting on the plane it's because they don't care they don't care there's parents that sell their daughters bro
they don't give a fuck
You act like every parent cares about their kid, bro
There's people that have kids just to fucking sell them
Sarky there's some stories right now on YouTube and and I've seen them before and it's interesting because of these white
Model girls they go to Dubai to meet the rich prince. It's wanted, you know, and they'll spend money on them
They use
Let's only document over back. Okay
And but they use them as like a sex toy. Yeah, they do do that. They're dead, but it's like family
I mean, but they they say it's hard for the family to be in touch with them from another country
Dubai and they're like clean fairs or
and
I've seen like
More like that. It's going on now
It's been going on
Our crystal just try to call my text now number
Did you hear the ringing because it froze my I'm on my phone on on on panel
Yeah, I just went ahead and
Block I hit block on it. Did you hear it ring or no because it froze my phone. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, you did hear
Yeah, that was her calling from her phone number
Yeah
Okay. Yeah, she's calling right now. Probably saying that's asking about me. But you know, can you can you remove that line?
Can you ask me see that's what she'll do and then all of a sudden there she goes against me doing now
She's saying this and this in line. So no, I gotta show my proof, bitch
Yeah, try to call me just now fucking bit five eight. Well, I can't talk to everybody has it
Yeah, and then what answer she's like, yeah, I'm sorry. It's them
It's Jamie and Nancy and Ella and and Astro. I you know, I knew she wouldn't know good
It's like well, why do you reach out to everybody?
You don't like anybody and you reach out to all of us and I'm not guys and you can respond to the chat if you want because
You know I'm not hiding people sit unless they say so they say certain things. What did they say? What did they say?
Well, I just timed out Bay for like, you know 30 seconds because Bay is like, oh, you know
No surprise here. Like, you know, they're all PDF stuff, you know, it's like so I just say, you know, Bay and I have our own
I don't even know but what everybody's a PDF
Yeah
Yeah, why would a PDF want to expose a cannibal PDF?
It doesn't make no sense, it doesn't make no sense.
You know what?
Okay, so go ahead.
So Maya, so what are you saying?
You watched Live Unedited.
I watched the Live Unedited thing and I didn't see the there, there.
That's the point.
I saw.
There's nothing there.
So it was edited together, right?
It was heavily edited together.
Yeah, it was edited, yeah, it was edited.
Yeah, but you know what they're saying about that at the Epstein files there was somebody on CNN just recently they were on there and they were like well where are these files we were shooting already got in the Epstein files what are they hiding
Right, I mean they're out now millions of gigabytes of stuff. I mean there's like, you know, you can go through it
There's videos and all probably a lot, but um, yeah
But I've only seen one video clip of the man like in a deposition and then there's a guy walking around
It looks just like him right now, too. Like it looks like yeah, they're saying he's a lot
I mean, we're pretty sure he's alive. I'm sure the death was fake. What do you think about that?
Do you think the death was faked or you're either assassinated or he's not yeah
No, I think they did kill him in there because they don't like
No, he wasn't he wasn't no he he wasn't no where
I'm not doing anything wrong either Maya just by having people talking a conversation
Yeah, why are they so mad tell them to get up and who's this butterfly dude?
Who's that with the SWAT team like see that's a that's a threat. That's a threat. Look a picture of a SWAT team, dude
Like what is that?
Yeah, but see like this
Maybe that's just a murder. There's no when they say oh mercenary assassin
There's no such thing, bro. That's just a fancy word for a murderer, bro
Right, and that's exactly why the aliens are gonna be taking over God is done with us humans
So the aliens are on their way
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, I'm ready to date an alien. I think I'm I think I'm done with human beings. I mean, it's like
He's a sniper in the military in Afghanistan. So yeah, he's as far as I know the person's been nice in my chat
I mean, it's like I don't know who anybody's real identity is, you know, of course
But you know as far as he's been pretty respectful in my chat
And so, you know, I mean, it's not I'm not here to like, you know, attack anybody in the chat and or attack attack mods or anything
But we can have a conversation. That's the whole point
if like, you know, controversial anybody is,
I'm willing to talk to controversial people.
I'm willing to, and they're willing to,
questions asked, they're willing to have people come up
and talk with them and stuff like that.
But nobody is going to, yeah.
So we're gonna change the subject.
We don't want anybody to get PSG.
Hey, is that a sage you got in your hand,
or is that a born?
I got a cigar, I got a cigar.
Oh, I was gonna say.
I got a cigar, but I do have, do I have any?
I do have a little bit of charcoal left and so I'll light up some some incense and maybe we'll clear clear the air
We can like talk about yeah, exactly
Okay, so yeah, so okay, maybe the mercenary is not the right word
But it's one of those people hired by you know the government to go out
Doesn't have to be the government bro or a government not not the US government
I forgot the word you exact word you use but you know, I don't want to
He's like, oh my gosh, I'm not gullible. Okay. Bye butterfly. I'll see you later. Okay. So anyway
Yeah, so ETSD from what from Afghanistan that it was that was in shit, bro fighting a bunch of fucking goat farmers
The fuck with weak ass guns
That ain't shit, bro. Try fucking going up against fucking drones and fucking
Missiles and shit, dude. Try that
I saw the Taliban recently on TV and they're riding around in bumper cars and and in wrestling and stuff like that and jumping on trampolines
I mean, I don't even know what's going on
Posting an Instagram video or a Facebook video and they get the coordinates from that Facebook video and send a cruise missile to blow you up, dude
Right now. I mean there's yeah, there's there's really a weird stuff going on in the world and
I'm a peaceful person. I prefer
Peace, but you know, it's like you have to fight and
Defend ourselves and you know, anyway, here we go. There we go. Yeah, I helped take over
It's called
What is it called buck move?
It was the battle of buck move bro that town where they seize that town and it went on to like fucking like
Five months just just a meat grinder dude up close, bro. Yeah meat grinder, dude
I mean, I just watched something terrible about the other the obligareb, and I don't remember that that situation
Yeah, it's like terrible and you know, there's a really a lot of sick stuff going on
Oh, yeah, I saw that that chick was making the dude fucking
humiliate himself and shit
They still do that shit
yeah i know i know it's like you know and even police will you know our you know some police
are corrupt i mean there's a certain number i got beat up by the cops when i was like 12 or 13
years old bro the cop picked me up and slammed my body into the hard tile floor of like a hard
floor and he slammed me hard almost killed me dude yeah because he's all what is the back of
my shirt say he's all he think i'm done he's all what is what does my shirt say and it said apd gang
And I was all f a pd f a g unit and he grabbed me bro, and he slammed me dude on
Like my whole body dude like my chest landed chest first dude on the tile
To we to rough around to use the wheel they're trying to wield their what they think
Bro, I wish I would run into that dude now be like yeah, I wish I could see him now
But like hey remember you remember that little kid that you body slammed and almost killed
You know what I mean, uh-huh. I don't know so I want to run into him now
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, and it's like I mean I've been arrested a bunch of times
I mean it's like not for nothing ever serious
Nothing for like over a couple days and it's nothing no felon. Yeah ever like people are gonna say
Oh, you know this person's been arrested like just because you're getting arrested. That doesn't mean anything. It's like I mean
You actually do, you know, it's like, you know, and so so many kind of everybody's been arrested.
Everybody's been arrested, dude. The only people I know that hasn't been arrested is my mom.
That's like the only person I know that hasn't been arrested. Everybody else. Yeah. My parents, my sister.
And that's it
Yeah, yeah, my brother. Yeah, one of my brothers has never been arrested. Yeah, I mean pretty much
I'm like the one I'm like the one of my family who has but you know, it's like it's been for very stupid things and
Nothing ever that had a victim attached to it, right? It's like and so, you know, but people can't just like say
Oh, there's either it was no no victims or nothing
victimless crime so yeah, yeah, so I mean it's like we can the most people can relate to like knowing that the justice system
Is like a little bit overzealous, but they don't have backgrounds either at all except for my younger brother
For you I that my mom paid for to get removed. I guess I don't know long time ago
Apparently I'm going to jail now they said that I'm going to jail now that I'm gonna be they said
2026 Brandon's going to jail
For what? I haven't done anything. I haven't done anything wrong. Go to jail for what?
Right. I know exactly. I mean, it's like you have no violent crimes or anything on your...
Or you said you don't have a...
Ain't nothing gonna happen. Ain't nobody gonna...
What are they gonna do? Oh, go pick this guy up in New Mexico for doing all this and that
On live like a live stream like you don't yeah
those people like that like fire and you know what you know what I bet you would get him put in a prison for that if
I were to go to APD and say that I'm gonna sue you bro that my life is in danger and this keeps happening and it keeps on happening
Which have documentation and I said you were handed on a silver platter a perpetrator
And you've done nothing to protect me to do my job.
I can sue the fuck, and I bet you've already do that.
Contact Internal Affairs.
I guarantee you that mother fucker would get hammed up dude and I might do it keep keep trying to fucking play that little empty empty threat game saying that I'm going to jail bro i really will put you in jail
Brandon you should hit a hit up as JC and he'll get you in touch with his mom because she knows exactly where to go or what to do or who to talk to
about him because only she can help with she can help with that directly
because he's not supposed to be doing this yet and he's still doing it and then he's
hiding and then even using crystal interrupting power.
Let me say I'm going to jail. Why would I be worried about going to jail? I'm not on video
doing the legal shit. They are. I know. Yeah. Why would I be worried? Why would I be worried about
I've done nothing wrong?
No, it's all in look. This has been going on for years though, too. It's like come on shit get over it
It's a lot of hearsay
You know and just people like I was repeating what they've heard. Yeah
We're using the past and
For harassing people who am I harassing I don't harass anybody just because I make videos and talk about people. That's not harassment, bro
And it's usually only people that have harassed you heavily, right?
Yeah, yeah, exactly, exactly, and they're on video, dude.
Right.
I mean, that's the thing it's like Brennan does have, you know, evidence of people doing these things and it's like
And what it's Brandon said Brandon might say things, but it's like these people are actually doing things
Oh, like, you know, and it's like, you know, nobody really cares about that
I mean, it's like it's such a double standard and you know, people have to remember, you know
Like there's trauma involved in in like this bullying and in this harassment that we've all experienced and and so
We might react, but it's like you're not seeing the actions against us first or considering that
Yeah, it's part of their their own part in the harassment
Sometimes they're used as like these flying monkeys and they don't even know it right there just yeah, yeah
And so you know just always look for like you know look beyond the surface of what's going on because there's other stuff going on
Like you know, it's pretty obvious
I know that they're mad and desperate when they when they make these threat when they start making the threats
Yeah, that's how I know that they're mad, dude, and lately they've been evidence. It's not anything. It's not it's not it's just threats and it's just like to
Intimidate yeah, they think it's gonna make me go silent or disappear like oh, I need to hide. You know what I mean? Yeah
And it's like, you know, and we've been all of us have been like so docks heavily and then it's like but then everybody else is gonna go
Like oh my god, we docks because it's like we use somebody's you know
Picture without you know a phone number or name or anything to it. Yeah, we're gonna sit or exactly
Oh, it's like there's a big double standards and uh, like I got I get away with nothing
You're like really and I get away with I don't get away with anything even think that I haven't done I get oh
Yeah, if I if I have been doing shit out of already get caught up bro because
Right. They already did try to get me in trouble. This swagger that lives here
He said that I was lying about him having a child abuse charges, bro
And they fucking press charges on me, bro
They said I was lying and then it got dropped because I told the judge
I was like well, he does have child abuse charges, right and the judge is like oh go look it up
And then they dropped it right and so yeah, but it's like why would you even like?
Yeah, why would they they think they're gonna give away because that's how like
They are they they think that they can just get away with anything because they probably have like a lot of the time
You know and probably people just oh, well, you know, they're popular
They you know, it's things like this and it's like just because
Somebody doesn't have like the herd of people because remember most people are sheep most people and most people are just believe whatever
They're here and you're right
They're puppets and why would you be a puppet of Kate? Look at her. I need to show her pictures, bro
Her ankles bro are like like hooves dude
Tinkles. No, don't show her pictures
But she's saying that you know, she puts me on the on the street naked, you know with a yeah
She abuses psyche tells people to go swat him to report
Yep
Totally turned on me and I didn't yeah, I wasn't even why
Because of because I guess because you know, she doesn't like Brandon and so she
She just turned on me and started calling her predator protector and then it's like organized this boycott
She has told her or Benjamin working for her and you know other people and then she has like, you know
Like it is like big crowd of trolls in her chat that just went on like
Talk about me and where I live and and I should be you know victed from my own
You know my house and my family should like you know just own me and all this kind of stuff
And it's none of their business and so it's like when that they had brought up at all. Oh my god
You know you're bringing up this and this and this and this and it's like
We didn't I didn't bring anything up, you know, I can't control every look comes out of anybody's mouth
You know, I can just say
you know, let's not like not bring other people's families into things that and I don't and I just don't know
Sometimes then it's like, you know, there's a lot happening at once. So but you know
She's the one that exposed all that she's the one that tried to get sympathy say about her son's a dwarf
She's the one that posted his birthday party. She posted all of that
Yeah, I mean it's like you really I think parents really should like think twice about like being in like
some of these online communities, it's like there's a lot of weird shit going on, and it's almost like you know you're almost asking for trouble being in some of these communities, there are real weirdos in these communities, like real weirdos, and it's just because you know.
Very weird, very dangerous weird people and nothing to lose bro.
Right.
They don't have a life.
And then like the people that aren't doing anything they tend to get like they tend to be like, you know
Like get out quieter or maybe awkward or just like it perceived in some way to be an easy scapegoat or victim
I'm used to being a blame for all these kind of things that I have nothing to do with and so, you know
It's like just and I'm allowed to have whoever I want on my show
I think she was trying to tell me you can't have you can't have them on your show
Or else we're gonna do this because the community decided this
I'm not I was never accepted by any community. I'm like a lone wolf, but uh, so I'm here on my own on my own show
I'm not going to other shows and doing this kind of stuff and so and that's you know
So I don't understand like why I'm not allowed to and I am actually I am allowed to have whoever I want on my show
And do whatever I want and if there's consequences in terms of like some of this troll community not coming into my chat
It's like the trash took itself out. I'd rather not have
Most of these trolls here and I used to kind of look see clips of you and all this and that it's already bro
This is already going back a year. Yeah, they were already trolling you. They were already abusing you
They were already mocking you bro
Already, I also have a lot of them like a lot of trip kick is like very favorable to me
Yeah, you know, it's yeah, but I'm not I'm not I'm not well
I've seen though. I've seen beta streams and other people saying that saying that you have shit cat shit all over your house
Yeah
And now it's just become a thing is like don't don't don't get don't give them in your clout
You know, that's because yeah, it's because I have a you know
And I have a cat door and stuff like that and so the cats can go
And so it's like I don't even have that like it but they have they're their animals like locked inside the house
And they're talking about oh my house must smell and stuff like that
But actually, like my cats are like trained to go outside.
You know, they're not dogs, dogs will go inside.
Like, you know, and the, like this person in a case at last night.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I didn't know how the, how, how his house smells with all that cat spray.
You can say that with anybody with a pet.
You can say that about that.
But it's like, and if they repeat it, and they take pictures and they have to AI
the pictures of me just to make them.
And then people, and then like Bita knows this one picture that was shown with
like this fancy house behind me was on a real picture.
because her friend made that, Sweet Pea made that.
And she was like, oh my gosh, look at that.
And it's like, she knows it's fake.
She's like saying, if you're kidding, it's real.
And the dumb chats are like, oh my God, yeah.
There's like an echo chamber.
Whatever and so I don't even care that they're like, I don't want to be
An echo chamber they're wack like look at Sam Man's stream
Playing music bro Sam man uses bots you think there's fucking 200 people watching that
Yeah, the same people chatting but that he uses bots and then he pretends to get donations
You just go, shut up to the car, shut up, you're getting no fucking dough, and I'll
rub your dick and you'll be saying who it was from.
Right. He'd be bothering him. And so he, he like, uh, he said, Oh, yeah, well, someone
just sent me $15, you know, even though it's like $25, he's like, Oh, someone's gonna
be 15. And then ghosts is like, can I see the proof? And he's like, Oh, well, no, you
know, don't, you know. And so, um, you know, it's, it's ridiculous. Like, Oh, I can't
talk to my, my donators or whatever. But it's like, you know, some donators do prefer
to be anonymous, but it's like,
If they're on here donating you then they have a fucking username on YouTube, right?
And it's like, yeah, usually you can use their name and it's like it's not even their real name. And so
Cash app
The thing is it's like some people do go after the donators like a particular because they get jealous like I know Q
would like try to like harass donators and and you know the other Q
Like, uh, and, you know, or people will harass donators and then shame them into, because they would all say, oh ghost, you're gay because you donated a psyche.
And so it's like, so, uh, so it turns into like something where it's like, it turns into something negative for them.
And then it's like, and then they, and they'll try to get the person in their chat and stuff like that to don't.
And so it's like, it's like really, uh, ridiculous.
It's like a lot of, I don't want to get pranked on you.
You know, it's all, it's all, it's all bullshit, dude.
Yeah.
And where's Q45 where all these dudes at now? They're so silent even crystal where they at
All night and all morning
Other people she won't do it on her own any porn bomb for twice on her own show
Yeah, nobody likes her. Yeah. Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, and she's like, you know, just using her. Yeah, using it
Just using her. Yeah. Yeah, they're using her and they laugh at her behind her back and and Q even porn bombed her twice
Yeah, on her own live on our own life. I mean he tried to poor mom me, but I just I just had the
She's desperate for him and making a I pictures of them together, you know, she doesn't have no man and she never
has and look at all those videos and all those guys that she brought over to place and she was
always calling the police and that's the next thing on Monday. Remember Monday I'm going on private
all those videos on her and you'll see Chelsea and the guys she tried to put in jail and then the
stuff that I shared from that lady that busted her.
But the fake everything because she she's still around she has a huge following because she covers crimes now
She's not she said she doesn't want to
You know visit that rabbit hole again with crystal because she was one that called crystal out
I mean, I was playing I was playing like a true crime video like just commenting on it the other night
And then it comes up right away and says what's it? What is this shit? You're playing and I was like one
I like I don't I'm into true crime and I enjoy she's like
Well, what do you think you are? Some kind of vigilante? I mean, it just doesn't even make sense.
Yeah, Bita was saying that. Yeah, but what's funny is that, you know, yeah, it's like,
so they'll try to like, so they, when I start the drama back up and everything, they're like,
oh, this, but it's like, that's all they, that's all they like. They don't like anything besides
they're trying to like, you know, make me into like, some kind of like drama streamer. I was like,
that was never intended. And then they're like, when I'm not, you know, they try to stop that and then
But then when I do my own thing they just slander everything else I do and it's like and so and people like unfortunately
They don't believe like a lot of stupid shit and uh, so I'm pretty much had it. It's like, you know with uh, the
Yeah, the drama community. What is it? You're saying that you don't look at everything you've looked at everything that they've sent you about me, bro
Exactly, you have different topics
Yeah, you don't talk about everything's interesting things, you know that people are interested all she's about is drama and
Trying to get up on people and line and you know just I'm good
There's so much out on her for more ex-friends
I mean, people are like, okay, I'll prove this to you,
I'll prove this to you.
And then I, so I had to look at this like video
and I was like, there's nothing there.
If I can come to my own conclusions about things,
or if I, you know, but it's like,
and so I'll see things differently
because they were so sure Tommy and James is like,
oh, it's an open and shit.
But this is, but some of these people are the same people
that have been bullying me the same time at the same time.
And so do I really want to like listen,
I have to like listen to them or take their word for thing.
And it's like, and I know how they operate.
anything about
Actually really the thing with you. Oh look gambles in your chat. You would know about Luis and oofy. You know about oofy
What about him? That's not me. Why are you mentioning other people?
Why would you bring up another dude? Those are other to those are two full-grown men, bro?
What do they have to do with me? Whatever they done?
Yeah, and why is
Extort Aaron Carter or like yeah, Carter to like, you know
Having enough problems then you're going out you're going he's going on there saying oh well
You're a pedophile Aaron. You don't you know that you are you know?
Yeah, you are you are because you know, I was like, you know pretending to be a 15-year-old girl asking for a dick pic and yeah
It's like okay. Well, that sounds like you know some kind of like weird doesn't sound like
Yes, what on one of those calls that I recorded crystal on she's telling me there that he finally told her recently after he was on her live with her or whatever that she admitted that Aaron was never a pedophile.
Right
Kills people killed I mean it has people you know targeted and there's people that are crazy thing
Oh my god, we gotta save the children blah blah and I'm gonna play on the calls wait till you hear that cuz she said it on the
Call every was recording all the calls with her on that text now number
Know I mean, I think all again has is like it's gonna be all out again like last time and then she left because I called her out with the
Recordings and what really happened with Gabe and all that and then she left
But I just want to know what the point of it is is it to get them to unalive themselves or is it to like you know to blackmail?
I don't understand what the point of I can just get you bro. It's sick. I think just for you, bro
Trying to feel their audience because that's all those people are became his audience after
Right, and that's like, you know, and it's like what whatever it's like, you know, they can they can steal
There's an audience to be stolen like the audience is like that dumb just to believe whatever is being said then I'm happy
They're not I don't want a bunch of like followers like really I want but I want like
Yeah, they're like leaders and like smart people and that was funny if I'm a pedo at so many DMs of his mods
Glazing me bro saying oh you're doing so good. Good job Brandon this and that
But how was it it's not a buddy troll bro? No, they were fucking on my fucking dick, bro
It's not a buddy troll bro. That's not how a buddy troll works, bro
With Aaron like that's how he was operating. He goes. Yeah with him and Aaron now with me
This fucker wanted me to get my foot off his fucking neck, bro
Okay, well, I actually wanted I know that there was like, you know, you are like the same age and stuff
And so maybe there was like some kind of felt like there's
like
The war to be over bro. He wanted the war to be over dude, and then and then me not figure anything out about him
Well, yeah, I mean it's like
I mean, I've seen very weird things. I mean it's just like
His own mom the predator like I said, why don't you go in there in the next room and catch the person that's in the next room next to you?
Right, I mean it's like I mean it's like yeah, how does that is he like it like you know when you do it to him?
It's like it's exactly like you and people have no empathy really and it's like then that's why that the karma comes in
It's like because eventually you'll experience what you put other people through it has to be like that or else
You know that's how our spirit grows sometimes
So it's like what so don't like just mistreat people for no reason
It's like basically I can't think of anything Eric Carter have done to this person to deserve what?
treatment of him because he was like you know pretty shook from having these
accusations and like you know they got kind of like it was obviously some kind
of weird setup or something like that and then you can tell how fake he is I
mean he was just so fake I mean it's like
It's ridiculous, you know, I never met him, he instantly started to attack me saying I'm an animal abuser without knowing me or anything, you know, right.
So it's like he's they're just jumping on the bandwagon, right. It's like, I mean, please, it's like so, so stupid.
Anybody that knows me, like, like knows the truth, but it's like, it's so sad.
People that actually had thought knew me.
Will it fall for the so so what it so what have you not seen about me that they're saying that you don't know about me that you
Haven't seen like what I see every
You've seen everything. Yeah, they said yeah the branding Q loved kids YouTube channel, right? You saw that right?
I mean, it's all slander to me. I mean, that's it. It just looks like slander. It's like because the one would say
Oh, just like oh, he looks kids. They would say oh, here's exactly the victim and here's what happened
But that there's no victims. There's nothing. It's just like a bunch of bullshit. It's like really. Yeah
Oh, I know who that is in chat. That's fucking uh, that's the fucking remember the Australian method
That he was playing he was crying about how he made all those videos about me
Lying about me for gamble and he doesn't get why gamble so obsessed with me. What about you?
If all was so bad, then why were you my little buddy then bro?
Why were you giving me all the information on your leader gamble?
Yeah, why were you exposing him that he never met his fiance if i'm a pedo and i'm so bad
Why were you talking to me all fucking night? Why were you talking to lazy run?
Why were you giving me info? Yeah, and he's actually said the only fucking reason why
right because you had no fucking discord to go hang out in that's subru that's
silver subi subru andrew cats in fucking australia and he's mad i got his info
keep it up bro i'm gonna contact victoria police bro and let them know everything you've done andrew
keep it up bro keep it up yeah that's andrew cats uh he's a failed game dev bro he was a
game developer and and fucking failed no you're not no and then that's what they always say oh i'm
Yeah, it's so easy to tell dude. It's so easy to tell bro like even I can't they make it easy the way they talk they all talked
Yeah, it's so easy man. KZ came on yesterday. This guy KZ who everyone thought was dead and everything
Yeah, he's like yeah, he's a he came in with a fake voice and instantly I said is that KZ like instantly
I I'm like really good at voices and stuff and it was him
I mean it was like instantly I you can't like you can't hide who you are sometimes, you know, it's like
It's pretty obvious. Yeah, if you know if you know, yeah, this butterfly six, too, that's one of them, too
That's a troll, bro
I was like always a little bit suspicious because it just seemed like yeah, it was just weird
I mean it's like they just showed up randomly like I don't I don't really get that many new people
just showing up and then being so yeah and stuff like that and then people went oh you do tarot
and it's like I don't even advertise tarot like really tarot on this particular channel and so
it's like to come in and say oh this this this it's obvious like so I always like kind of know
I basically have very few people that I can trust like uh because you know most people are
scam and I mean it's like and it's like really not fooling anybody but I'll play along for a while
just to let them you know expose themselves because that's what I like to do I like to let people
eventually expose themselves if there's something there and they they always will because you can't
really hide that kind of stuff so anyway and look at this guy here's some guys named gambler cats
Yeah, I mean, it's like they would be I mean
Bringing up the way I know it's because he's a simp and he got cooked
He got cooked and he was obsessed with the girl that gamble raped and that's why gamble
Turned an 86 and banished cats
From his from DX from his community because I went into a gamble. I was like, hey, you know your top mod is
Fucking simping for the girl that said he raped her, right?
And then that's when he banished him and then he started becoming my friend in Q army and giving me all the info about gamble dude
And then now they're back. He went crawling back to go do more free labor. He was crying on that video
Remember? Oh, I was doing all these videos for gamble about Brandon and he was bragging that it was free labor
That's the dude
He'll always that's how I know it's him. He'll always bring up that girl that gamble rate, bro
He'll always bring her up, bro. Who is that? I know it's you because nobody knows about her. Nobody knows about her, bro
Yeah, like I said, they'll eventually reveal themselves like if you give them a rope, right?
No rain was a girl that was coming. Okay when I had my vertical stream
Rain was some girl or whatever that was came in my stream
And fucking I guess they found her Instagram and they and then she's like all these people are messaging me
He's like gambles messaging me to groom me and shit, dude
That's who rena is
And then I only sent them one DM saying hey just go and post tell him block them and then post all the evidence
That they're contacting you and then that was it
That was it bro
No, you message her you message her she even said she's all these weirdos are contacting me
Fucking creep fucking pedophile
Cats, what about Daniel Karen is cancel here? You know about Daniel. Yeah, I remember. Yeah
I remembered the cuz because when we looked him up during COVID it showed that it was a kid named Daniel
And you have some kind of video. I think I'll share that on Monday. I have a video of him talking about that
Yeah, I remember it was all up there and they were going at him about it
I have a video of gamble half nude bro with a little
eight-year-old boy bro oh yeah in the water yeah i saw that that's horrible and he was over there
mooning for him in front of his dad and his dad was going off on him i think we now let's share
that i think she was like exactly
Yeah, she shared it. It was like a story. I'll share it, you know Monday. I'm gonna I'm gonna yeah
That shocked me and that was recent. That was no don't even share it because that's what got my channel taken down
For it said for child sexual exploitation, bro, and it said they were
They said it was illegal bro that I was showing child abuse, bro
And it was a video of Gamble
Making it clap shaking his fucking ass in a song showing his asshole to a little kid
Yeah, I saw that. Yeah, damn
Humping on it. Humping on a fat dude saying oh, you're so good poppy
Goatee and a five-row this four feet away
Yeah, yeah, right behind him and he was right moaning for him like he was
Practically in his face and the dad started going off on him
I mean the animals wrecked him and he was and he was smiling at the dad like look what I'm doing your boy
It's like that was sick
Yeah, they literally said
The dad literally said he's all what are you doing you're gonna traumatize my little boy was yelling at him
Yeah, and he didn't care and he was still smile. Yeah. Yeah, I do stupid. Yeah exactly and he
Look at that was obvious because everybody that saw that was blown away. It's like damn and it's like I'm thinking damn
That's recent. That was like, oh, they're saying that I'm banned for showing Trisha's daughter
How you how would you get banned for that, bro?
That means that she would get down for it.
Yeah, she shows her own daughter.
How the fuck are you gonna get taken down for showing you videos that are already on YouTube, bro?
That's not a violation, but no.
Showing a 35-year-old man,
a predator like William Witt Ganball,
showing his asshole to a little kid in public,
that's different, bro.
That's different.
With the dad right in front of him. Yeah, but the kids dad yelling at him. If you didn't do nothing wrong, bro
Why did the little boys dad want to beat your ass if you did nothing wrong?
predator
It is a predator did
Yeah, so gamble tell everybody about how your top mod cats
Turned his back on you bro to go simp for the girl that said you raped her
Well, resident even turned on him because they kicked her and somebody else I think moldy
Because they were doing some shady shit behind his back and in their mod
DC group or whatever and I have communication from resident in text where she was threatening to use what she took from his
their private
group or whatever and
She had she was going to expose them and all and she was pissed off because he kicked her out
Yeah, and then now I heard that there she was she's on his kick account donating to him now
And I remember when she had no money and you know, she she could be big. He could be donating
I think he donates to himself honestly
Yeah
And then now she's over there kissing his ass when she was talking shit about him and how she could expose him and the
Secret she has on him and and she was ready to expose them and yeah, I have all of that on my computer
I saved all that communication
Yeah, I didn't trust her and then she had a tomb raider, which was one of his best mods
Kit from DX
Lion and saying that the tomb raider never had cancer. She does
She's in the myoclinic
And they're giving her a medication that includes ketamine to help
You know with with the cancer
So that's that's fucked up. She was a good person. I talked to her
She even changed her name on YouTube, but yeah, she's a mod for a streamer that we were not too familiar with
Yeah
Yeah, we'll be around much longer. I guarantee you dude
We're gonna hear one of these days that he overdosed or something cuz look at him
I put my money on it, bro that he won't he's gonna be the next Aaron Carter
Does he do drugs? Yeah, he does all kinds of drugs, uh
Robo Robo tussin fucking all kinds of weird shit, dude mess
Yeah, it's crazy crazy crazy world and uh, yeah, I mean, yeah, so and they're all on YouTube
I never revenge porn anybody when did I revenge porn somebody you fucking idiot who did I revenge porn?
You're the cats is the one you're the one that fucking leaked your whole thing
You're a simp, bro. I don't talk to that shit. I have nothing to do with her, bro
What the fuck you talking about bro fucking dude is so desperate, bro fucking simp, dude
Fucking mess head dude. He admitted he this dude. He literally used to tell me that he's miserable
He's on math. He can't sleep. He's paranoid. He's losing his mind that he's scared of discord
He's paranoid all this shit, bro. You're a punk, dude
Wow
Well, I'm gonna go ahead and drop off
We've been having nothing but rain all week long, but it's still cool. So it stopped finally
Okay, so I'll talk to you later. Okay
Good one you too. Hey
Okay, yeah, I'm probably gonna hop off to I got a charge on my headphones and shit
Well, thanks for coming on sharing your experiences in your story and I talking to you. Have a nice day
Oh, yeah, have a good one bro. Talk to you later. Thank you
Thank you. Okay, so if anyone wants to come up. I look in we can totally change gears now. I do have a
Do you have a new a new app out and I'd like to test it out with some people and so if you'd like to
Have your it's called it's a it's a it's a night it's a nightmare generator basically
But it's kind of a fairy tale themed anyone wants to come up. We'll see how the chest
Yeah, I'm at the point where it's like, you know, whatever what else can go. Hey, come on, baby
So, um, let's see. I'm trying to find the chat right now. Should I wrap up? I'm not sure. Let me see
Let's see
Let me just
Hear me and take a short short commercial break
Thank you all for being here. I think I'm participating. I think I think you modest shout out to the mods too and
I keep in keeping things good. Like I said, I'm willing to have anybody come up into their story because it's like the substance being
Done to me right now for really no reason is you know
So let's see
So I mean, I don't know most of these people. Oh shut up. Bathory. You know, you're an old kind
You're probably a man. I mean, it's like geez
Somebody find out who Bathory is. I mean, please. I mean this cunt predator protector. Oh my gosh
What am I doing? I'm throwing myself in a bulletproof vest in front of people,
or just having them on a public show. I mean, it's like, what, you're here. I'm an asshole
protector because you're in the chat. Oh, shut up. Oh, shut up. Yeah, I'm such an animal abuser,
aren't I? Oh, I know, I'm such an animal abuser. Oh, my cats hate me. Don't they hate me? Oh,
what do you do? Oh, my gosh, I'm so rough, aren't I?
Aren't I rough with my cats, you know when they would they even would they let me pick them up even I mean
I don't understand if I was such an abuser and yeah, oh, baby. Oh, hi, sweetheart
No, I'm such an abuser, right?
He feeds his cats to coyotes and doesn't spay a neuter well the Norse fixed and Lola's fixed and Rudy's fixed and so
What are you talking about?
bitch
Well, you know, you can have your own opinion about people you're allowed to but it's like, you know
Just make sure that you know, you know the whole story though
That's all I'm saying. It's like and if you people could come to their own conclusions like I don't care like, uh, right
I have nothing to all I'm doing is have toasty a show, you know, so
I mean, if you have a problem with that, go ahead.
But yeah, here's my abused cat.
This is Lenore.
She's very abused and very unhappy and all that stuff, right?
Kate says, my cats eat my scabs.
Well, if Kate says it, it must be true.
It must be true if Kate says it.
Hi mermaid. How are you? And I know I mean, I know that there was a little crossover because I thought
Yeah, I mean, yeah, but look how they're going to unhappy and you know the Norris fix were you fixed?
Were you fixed immediately when I got you so you've never had it?
You never had a baby, you know never had a baby, but Lola did right and I've had three liters of babies
You know three liters of cats
So that's why I had a lot of cats at once because I had five five were born at a day
So yeah, so that was like, you know, eight or nine cats, but you know what?
They're all happy and in good homes. Hi. Yeah, I mean, it's like what's what the fuck is wrong with some people good times
Docs Joe Shipley. Oh my gosh. Well, that's not very good to do
I mean, it's like I don't like how they're treating Joe Joe's a good guy and it's like then they're on beat is there was trying
This guy came up trying to say oh Joe is has done something
Yeah
Yeah, and Q has kittens. Who's not fixed? Yeah, exactly. Q has kittens, right?
I mean, I had kittens, but I raised the kittens, and I had tricks, and I had one of the kittens still,
and his name is Tux, and he comes in here, and he's loving it.
Oh, shut up, Bathory. You're such a dumb cunt. I mean, it's like you've been the same.
They're spayed and neutered. I mean you don't understand like some people are just like retarded. I think like especially this bath reperson
So, you know, I think that you're probably too dumb to be on the show. And so why don't you just kick rocks bitch?
There you go. Yeah, and you know
Exactly. I mean, it's like, jeez, it's like, and who it has anybody here not had a cat pass away or a cat
You know run away or a dog a cat run away, you know, there's like on the next door
This is a nice neighborhood, right? And I'm supposedly the biggest trash in the neighborhood
There are literally hundreds of missing cats, you know, and it's like
So it eventually sometimes it happens, you know, eventually what happened to you and then it's like, I hope, you know
You don't get treated like I get a get treated by some of you. Okay?
I mean, it's like jeez. Yeah. What did you do to his kid? I mean I didn't I didn't wasn't there like a dead cat
There's dead dead dead cats involved with them and stuff like actual like you know leaving them in car and car
He's in a car. How can you have kittens if he's living in this truck? I don't understand
But you know and then he's like oh look and then oh coo coo coo coo my cats have a nice beautiful neighborhood and it's like
You know, unfortunately there are coyotes, you know, and so there are dangers, you know, but there's dangers to
You know, having your kids go outside too, you know, there's, there's strangers and stuff like that, right?
And then it's like, are you going to keep your kids locked in the house and never let them leave?
And, you know, it's like, you have to let, yeah, this is Ms. Lola, I mean, Lola, do you hate me?
I'm a bad, I'm a bad cat dad, Lola, am I?
No.
See, she said no.
Hey, money for 20, so money for 20, I'll make you a deal.
Okay, I don't like being hidden by.
Bronze bitch or whoever that was and I do like coming to your show, but I can't come any more
It's like, you know, I'm gonna be hidden every time by bronze bitch
So I'm gonna mod you. I
Appreciate if you repay the favor so I can at least be in the chat. I'm respectful in the chat
I always said was hello in the chat yesterday
I don't know if you saw but and he's like laughing and bragging and that uh, you know that I
Can't be in there because you know, he's like the police of your chat
For doing you know, he talks about feefies. He's in his feefies like I like I wouldn't even block him in any chat
And I and I test him right? Oh, there's Rudy too. Hi Rudy. Hi Rudy. Oh, you came running over to you. Oh
Rudy old man Rudy. I mean, yeah, are you abused? No
You're a sweet cat. You're very soft beautiful. You're not covered in fleas
You're happy, right? I mean the cats are well fed, well taken care of. I feed the cats before I feed myself
I mean, it's like Jesus. I mean just to be the things that people fucking say. I mean, it's just like so out of pocket
And yeah, I really hope that it's like, you know, when you people start saying shit about you like, which is like, sometimes I just like, well, respond and give them a little taste of their own medicine.
I even feel bad sometimes when I do, but it's like, but some of these people have done way, like, you know, I haven't done anything.
Like really, it's like, these people have done way, way, most actually done these horrible things.
And it's like, Oh, no, but they're, you know, the popular blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm just sick of this slanderous things, trying to fucking de-platform, calling me all kinds
of horrible, slanderous things that are most opposite of really who I am, that it's like...
You know, it really takes the fun out of the community or whatever community this is or whatever, I don't even know where I am.
I don't care if I'm alone on an island, but you know, what does Kate say?
Oh, well, he thinks things are going back to normal, but you know what?
Everyone go to his chat and just make sure to give a thumbs down and call him a predator protector.
And look at you little flying monkeys just doing exactly that.
I mean, so what is Kate, your mom?
I mean, is Kate, she's God to you or something?
I mean, I don't know.
I'm not trying to tell you what to do,
where to go to go bother her or do anything like that,
but you're so happy to go do it to me.
And how would you feel?
It's like, you have no empathy at all.
Like, I'm not talking to everybody here.
I'm talking to the people that they know I'm talking to.
You know, cause I do have good friends
and people that are keeping me,
keeping me basically alive in the difficult times, right?
Cause it's like, you know,
All I'm doing is having a show and it's like just the fact that I've never seen anybody have such a backlash that I've had and
People have done so much worse and it's like and it's like that's not even considered in that
But it's like oh, I'm just an easy target what because you think people think oh
Alright, the cats eat my scab. What's scab? I don't have scabs. I mean, it's like you're a scab
Because you're just a hanger on our bathory and you're just a cunt. I mean, you're probably fucking one of Kate's alts or something
Or Tony's. I mean, it's like, you know, the only person that thinks you're sexy isn't NorCal and he's, you know, older than Santa Claus
So, I mean, please
I mean, you're such a loser
I'm constantly, and you never offered me anything.
I mean, it's like, all these people,
so all some of these people have done is troll me,
and then they expect me to bow down and listen to them
and do what they want me to do.
If I want to have, you know,
if I want to have Jeffrey Epstein on my show,
I would have, you know, what if,
so if Michael Jackson was alive and you had a show,
and then Michael Jackson wants to come on,
just, and you know all his allegations,
would you have Michael Jackson on, you know, yeah.
I mean, it's like, jeez, I mean, it's so ridiculous.
I mean, what am I like fuck it? I'm sure you're probably worse than Jeffrey Epstein this point, right?
I mean, it's like and it's ridiculous. Okay, so anyway
Okay, just give me a couple minutes and I'll be right back. So
Yeah, or you know, you're welcome to be here or not. I mean, it's like jeez
I mean, I'm here to like have fun and it's like, you know, people some of these people are making it
absolutely like miserable, but
You know, just do your thing. I mean, it's like you're pretty
People pretty sad. Okay. Geez. There we go. We're back
testing testing
Anyway, I bet I do appreciate the people that have been supportive and understand
Cuz it's like, you know
Sweet understanding
See more to go friends. Okay. I love little shop of course, right? Okay
Yeah, it's sometimes I do it. I do wish I could like, you know, I
Play more
I'd love to show you a lot of stuff that I'm allowed to show because of copyright stuff, but
You know, I do have pretty good
Tasting different things. Okay. Let's let's see. Oh my god here. Here we go. Perfect. It's working now
Okay, just give me a second. I'm right back
Okay, yeah, you missed a lot. Yeah, I mean it's like I mean it's I mean it started off like a like pretty crazy, right?
Start off crazy. Oh, I still have like this this thing burning. I need to kind of clear. I think like mercury mercury
It's good. Yeah, we get a full screen. Okay. I want to show you the nightmare generator
So this is my new nightmare generator.
It's like, you know, Google had this thing where you could like, you know,
write a book about you and stuff.
And so, you know, I love, I used to love those books that they, you know,
they personalized, they put your name in and stuff like that.
And it would be like almost about you and stuff.
But actually, so this is even better than that because these are actually
completely personalized with images and beautiful artwork, actually.
You can save this forever.
Actually, I have even more than that.
I put in, put in an oracle.
And so you actually get a reading.
while you do it too, and your own personalized tarot card.
It works like I hope.
And so I'll show you my new app.
Okay, is it here?
Okay, well, you'll enjoy it, I promise.
Okay, so it's called Dreamweave Dark Tales,
and enjoy.
So if no one wants to come up, I will show you my own,
here you go.
See it. Okay, there we go. Okay, so dream we've dark tales, okay
So it's your fears your stars your story woven by the Oracle and to myth that was always waiting for you. Okay, so we
Initiate the ritual. Okay, there we go. So these first three picture names. So, you know, it's pretty easy
Just go you can use a fake name if you want. I don't care. Okay proceed
Okay, so name your shadow frequencies select up to three. So what are basically what are you afraid of? Let's see. I'll say dolls
let's see I'll say darkness okay and how about uh uh forgetting okay so let's go with those
I'll go with those just randomly okay select my stellar origin what's your sign okay capricorn
okay the best sign okay choose your archetype and these are fairy tale archetypes what red writing
big bad wolf sleeping beauty gretel hansel the wiki queen pied piper Rapunzel bluebeard
I'll be the Wicked Queen today, okay?
I'll be the Wicked Queen.
So it might make me a female, it's okay.
I'm willing to do drag in my story.
Okay, configure transmission tone.
So let's say, let's do a melancholic beauty.
I like that, okay?
Proceed.
And okay, so celebrate how dark do you want this?
How deep in the void do you dare to send?
So let's just do a confession, five scenes, okay?
Let's,
Put up the nightmare level. I know I can go to like 77% 77. Okay, perfect
And so then you just press enter in both the oracle and let's see what happens. Okay, and
While we wait, okay, there we go weaving the nightmare threats together traversing the forbidden archives
Okay, there we go the glass mausoleum of memory when the mountain goat climbs to the edge of the void and the porcelain weeps ink, okay
So you'll see it's beginning to generate some images and you know, it should come up pretty quickly
So this is 77. So yeah, there we go. And so then the images begin to generate so you get these personalized images
Okay, so the precipice of the goat
Psyche stands atop the obsidian crags of the Capricorn soul where the air is thin enough to snap like a frozen reed
Here the constellation of the seagull bleeds a cold silver light onto the jagged peaks reminding
Her, that she was born to climb, even if the destination is a hollow crown.
The wind carries a scent of ancient lavender and dust, the smell of a closet shut for
a century.
Down in the valley, the shadows move with the life of their own, licking the base of
the mountain.
Psyche watches as the darkness swallows the path behind her.
Rome, one must first forget the warmth of the sun.
The silence is absolute, save for the rhythmic clicking
of porcelain joints echoing from the caves below.
The descent leads Psyche to a subterranean cathedral of velvet and glass, row upon row
of dolls, sit on moth, eat and throne, sir eyes, native polished onyx, fixed upon her
with a terrifying static recognition.
Their cheeks are painted with a flesh of a fever that they can never catch, and their
mouths are frozen in tiny painted ores of perpetual surprise.
One doll wearing a miniature, shroud of lace, reaches out with a stiff, lacy arm.
Psyche smells the damp earth of a forgotten childhood.
These are not toys, they are vessels for every memory she has discarded, and...
Okay, I discarded Ed to keep her heart hard. They watch her with predatory patients of a spider
Their glass skin reflecting the flickering torchlight of her failing fading resolve. Oh, look at here's the images coming up
I wonder if it came up here yet. There's there's there's a capricorn consolation
There's me as a woman and drag there
And there's me looking in the mirror.
Oh, there's, look at, is that Gotti?
Gotti's there too, look at all the dolls too.
See, it's personalized in illustrations.
The mirror of the wicked queen.
In the heart of the dolls,
parlor stands a mirror, framed in thorns,
psyche approaches, her Capricorn stubbornness,
driving her toward the glass.
The reflection that greets her is not her own,
but that of the wicked queen,
a regal skeletal figure with a crown of bone.
The queen's eyes are void,
it's two pools of absolute darkness
that threaten to pull psyche's consciousness
into the nothingness.
to delete, the queen whispers, her voice sounding like dry leaves skittering across the grave.
The queen begins to peel a layer of silver from the mirror, and with it the memory of
Psyche's mother's face dissolves into a gray smudge. The tear is not in the pain,
but in the lightness that follows, a hollow space opens in Psyche's chest where a name used to live.
The erosion of the cell, the darkness expands no longer a mere absence of light, but a physical weight, thick as tar.
Psyche tries to recite her own name, but the syllables are like sand in her mouth.
She watches her hands, they're turning white, the skin hardening into a high gloss glaze.
Her joints begin to creak with the sound of a tightening screw.
The transition is visceral, the smell of turpentine, and wood glue fills the air.
She looks back at the dolls, and they are moving now,
scuttling across the floor like porcelain beetles.
They are eager to welcome their new sister.
Psyche realizes the wicked queen was never an enemy, but a prophecy.
The queen is the ultimate forgetting, the monarch of the void,
who reigns over a kingdom of nameless beautiful things.
And there's me on the throne, right?
The eternal stillness, the transformation is complete, Psyche sits upon the throne of
cold marble, her limbs locked in graceful eternal curve, her eyes are now two perfect
obsidian spheres, wide and unblinking, staring into the dark, the memory of the mountain,
the stars of the Capricorn, and even the sensation of breathing have slipped away into the ink
black velvet of the abyss.
A single doll climbs into her lap and rests its head against her porcelain breast, where
a heart once beat.
There is no more fear.
For there is no more Psyche to feel it, only the queen, cold and exquisite, presiding over a gallery of silent dolls, who remember nothing forever, the darkness is finally complete, a shroud that fits perfectly.
And here's a prophecy, everyone gets a prophecy, this is personalized, right?
So it says, Saturn builds your bones, Psyche, stone by stone.
But the tale showed you a tower so tall, its keeper forgot the ground, your ambition is holy.
your exhaustion is not a sacrament. Descend once a week. The mountain will wait. The still face
frightened you become because they do not choose and you can. Every fear of the lifeless is a
reminder that you are not. The queen's only sin was asking the mirror instead of herself.
You hold her crown. Stop pulling the glass. You already know
Who is the fairest in the life that is actually yours?
At 77% deep psyche, the void looked back and blinked first.
Carry that.
Whatever watches you this season should know
that you have been watched by worst.
Isn't that a fucking amazing, amazing story?
I loved it.
And so you can go in the archives,
you can print this out, save it, have it printed,
but whatever, I have to do some more work on it.
But,
I think it's pretty damn cool. Hope you like that. Yeah, Butterfly it's safe now. Butter butterfly butterfly come on out
Yep, you're gonna sleepy. We'll go to sleep big clips. I'm you know, you you always put me to sleep
You know imagine having to stay awake, you know entertaining you
Yeah, and what's your problem with that? No, you know poor stroke up, you know stroke up just got this
I don't know. Will he be able to keep his ebt with the
With with that I saw that episode of yours. I actually do look at your channel
I mean, it's like I would I will support people and stuff like that that the whole thing is it's like I had like
Kate and clumsy bean gang and Tricia Licious, they were all on my recommended channels on my thing.
I was supporting these people. I was like, you know, a cheerleader for these people and what?
They just turn on me because we have a disagreement about about somebody. I mean, it's like really
Really just just how shallow they were because it's like I'm actually not a bad guy. I'm like a
First pretty interesting
You know have a lot of experience. I'm not I'm not I'm no Cyrax
I'm not like, you know fucking gonna do phone sex with the you know person with a voice changer and believe it
You know, I'm not gonna go meet and you know drag queen at the shopping mall and get you know get I don't know
I mean, I mean, this is crazy. It's just crazy. Okay, but anyway, I have a
I have something to share with you. Okay, so the whole reason I started this channel. It's called cupidens
It was it's called psyche psyche awakens or whatever and people are like, what does that mean?
Okay
Well psyche is actually the name of a goddess, but she was actually a woman first and the beginning of the story starts out that
Venus got very jealous of psyche, right?
because psyche was this earthly woman and she was getting all these like
accolades and you know a lot of attention and people were you know worshiping her instead of worshiping the goddess and so
Venus has a son named Cupid, you know, he's like a little mischievous kind of evil considered sometimes
You know god because he makes people fall in love and do weird things
And so she sends she gives him an arrow and she's like oh strike
because like he would make her fall in love with a monster and
but he accidentally pierces himself and uh
He falls in love with her
and then uh
You know so then she goes their family goes the Oracle of Apollo and saying why why is she having such bad luck?
She can't find a man whatever, but every man would just look at her
But none of them would like you know be with her and
They said okay. We have to sacrifice from a mountain and so at this point in the story you can watch the first two
I already made the first two, but at this point in the story
she goes to the mountain and
Here we go
Enjoy this. This is the this is when she goes to the mountain to be sacrificed and what happens there
It's the part of part story part music. Okay. Enjoy
No, should I go? Is it the end of the stream? I don't know. What do you mean? It's awkward
go get a snack. I'm gonna get a snack too. What do I have to eat? Hmm.
Oh, how about this? These are my favorites. Do you ever have an egg in there?
Look at this. These are the best ones. Go get these at the store.
Shin noodles. I need a little bit. I need a little bit. I put an egg in it. I'll stay.
I'll stay for a little bit. Hold on. Wait a second. I'm just gonna put it on the hot water.
Do a reading. Here. This is perfect for the nightmare show. Hold on. I'll turn off the
You're okay? Okay. Yeah, I'll do a quick reading. And then this is called Todd Alcott's Horror Tarot.
Life, Death, Fate, Home, and the Cards. Okay, let me just turn off the background so you can see the
cards better. Everyone here gets a free reading. If you want a card, just let me know. Hold on.
Okay, that's horror themes. It's H-O-R-R-O. Okay, let's see. Is that okay? Okay, okay. Oh yeah,
Okay, we have the night of pentacles. Okay, so of all the nights and the night of pentacles is like
This he's the he's the slowest moving. He's a romantic guy. He brings gifts. He uh, he's maybe an earth sign
So someone coming towards you
um, kind of maybe slow it's taking a while to get there, but they're gonna stay for a while and uh,
they're really cool because they're earthly and uh, you know, they like to do uh,
you know activities and
Okay. Okay. Thank you. Thank you, Katie. Yeah, there you go. But there, but this is kind of scary, you know, I guess this is the Phantom of the Opera, I'm guessing, and there's Christine Dyer, right?
Phantom of the Opera, great, great in music, right?
But, you know, the Phantom of the Opera, I mean, he doesn't have the mask in this one. I think this is the original Phantom of the Opera. Okay, well, you know, there weren't just left like that.
Then, okay, thanks a lot. Have a nice day then.